{
    "id": "emi",
    "name": "Walmart & EMI",
    "description": "So, please check your level of learning in Walmart & EMI section !!",
    "passPercentage": "90",
    "mode": "wizard",
    "questions":[
        {
            "id": 1,
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "What is EMI?",
            "options": [
                {"id": 1, "text": "Equal Monthly Installment"},
                {"id": 2, "text": "Enterprise Membership Information"},
                {"id": 3, "text": "Enterprise Master Item"},
                {"id": 4, "text": "Economic Manufacturing Index"}
            ],
            "answer": 3,
            "score": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 2,
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "Which of the following is not a business entity of Walmart Inc?",
            "options": [
                {"id": 1, "text": "Walmart Stores"},
                {"id": 2, "text": "Marketplace"},
                {"id": 3, "text": "Sam's Club"},
                {"id": 4, "text": "GEC"}
            ],
            "answer": 2,
            "score": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 3,
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "Which of the below are business benefit of EMI?",
            "options": [
                {"id": 1, "text": "Visibility across business segments"},
                {"id": 2, "text": "Better enterprise level decision making"},
                {"id": 3, "text": "Business Automation"},
                {"id": 4, "text": "Streamlined Item Setup Process"},
                {"id": 5, "text": "All of the above"}
            ],
            "answer": 5,
            "score": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 4,
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "Which of the following is not a benefit of EMI?",
            "options": [
                {"id": 1, "text": "Customer-Driven Attribute Governance"},
                {"id": 2, "text": "Single, Unified Customer Facing Item File for the Enterprise"},
                {"id": 3, "text": "Suppliers can be excluded from Item creation process."},
                {"id": 4, "text": "Improved data quality and consistency"}
            ],
            "answer": 3,
            "score": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 5,
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "Identify the external stakeholder(s) of EMI?",
            "options": [
                {"id": 1, "text": "Sam's Club"},
                {"id": 2, "text": "Walmart International"},
                {"id": 3, "text": "Suppliers"},
                {"id": 4, "text": "None of the above"}
            ],
            "answer": 3,
            "score": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 6,
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "Identify which of the below is not a Key component of EMI",
            "options": [
                {"id": 1, "text": "Workflow"},
                {"id": 2, "text": "Attributes"},
                {"id": 3, "text": "Pre Item"},
                {"id": 4, "text": "ADS"}
            ],
            "answer": 4,
            "score": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 7,
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "What are the  4 main divisions of Walmart Business",
            "options": [
                {"id": 1, "text": "Walmart US, Walmart International, Sam's Club,  Walmart Global e Commerce"},
                {"id": 2, "text": "Walmart UK, Walmart International, Sam's Club, Walmart Global e Commerce"},
                {"id": 3, "text": "Supercenter, Neighborhood market, Walmart to go, Walmart Pick up grocery"},
                {"id": 4, "text": "None of the above"}
            ],
            "answer": 1,
            "score": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 8,
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "At what concept level are the items maintained currently in Walmart?",
            "options": [
                {"id": 1, "text": "Trade Item"},
                {"id": 2, "text": "Supply Item"},
                {"id": 3, "text": "Product"},
                {"id": 4, "text": "Core Product"}
            ],
            "answer": 1,
            "score": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 9,
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "What is the lowest level in trade item hierarchy?",
            "options": [
                {"id": 1, "text": "Pallet"},
                {"id": 2, "text": "Each"},
                {"id": 3, "text": "Case"},
                {"id": 4, "text": "Warehouse Pack"}
            ],
            "answer": 2,
            "score": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 10,
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "Order management and inventory management functions are benefits of which of the below concepts?",
            "options": [
                {"id": 1, "text": "Product"},
                {"id": 2, "text": "Core Product"},
                {"id": 3, "text": "Supply Item"},
                {"id": 4, "text": "Trade Item"}
            ],
            "answer": 4,
            "score": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 11,
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "Replenishment Method is part of which concept level",
            "options": [
                {"id": 1, "text": "Product"},
                {"id": 2, "text": "Offer"},
                {"id": 3, "text": "Supply Item"},
                {"id": 4, "text": "Trade Item"}
            ],
            "answer": 3,
            "score": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 12,
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "Which concept level is specific to Walmart Internal View?",
            "options": [
                {"id": 1, "text": "Core Product"},
                {"id": 2, "text": "Offer"},
                {"id": 3, "text": "Trade Item"},
                {"id": 4, "text": "Supply Item"}
            ],
            "answer": 4,
            "score": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 13,
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "question": "What is the the technology group in GeC called?",
            "options": [
                {"id": 1, "text": "Information System Division"},
                {"id": 2, "text": "@WalmartLabs"},
                {"id": 3, "text": "Walmart GEC"},
                {"id": 4, "text": "GEC Labs"}
            ],
            "answer": 3,
            "score": 1
        }
    ]
}



